OYELAKIN TAYO DAMOLA

DATA ENTRY ASSISTANT

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Data management with more than four years of experience in verifying complex data, database maintenance and producing daily, weekly and monthly reports using advanced Excel functions such as vlookup, basic knowledge of SQL, Power BI and other data analyst tools, Excellent time management and multitasking abilities. I am an enthusiastic, selfmotivated, reliable, responsible and hard working person.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Data Entry Assistant, 2020 till Date

APIN Public Health Initiatives [APIN]

No 1, Plot 8b Ondo Close, off Oshuntokun Avenue Old Bodija. Oyo State.

- Assisting HI Team in data cleaning and ensure data accuracy Ensure completion of patient's data record from registration point and updating patient's health records using OpenMRS.
- Ensure Data integrity and confidentiality
- Assisting Focal person to track Lost-to-Followup [LTFU] with Excel Linelist.
- Ensure concurrency of data between Database [EMR] and National Data Repository [NDR] with help VLOOKUP Excel Function.
- Regularly checking patients' record to know when due for drugs pickup and viral load bleeding.

Lead Data Manager, 2019-2020

Center for Integrated Health Programs (CHIP)

Lagos State University Teaching Hospital, Ikeja Lagos.

- Ensure all patients information daily get capture by used all relevant registers.
- Ensure all patients' pharmacy forms get captured.
- Generating daily Backups and XML Files.
- checked all register and forms for data completeness
- Enrolled and captured all Patients for Patient Biometric System [PBS]
- Generate daily and weekly report

Part-Time Lecturer, 2018-2019

The Polytechnic Ibadan Department of Logistic and Transport (Poly Consult), Ibadan Oyo.

- Prepared lecture guides for the class before lecture schedule period.
- Used Visual displayed diagram for more illustration in the class.
- Assessed the students through class assignment and test.
- Take attendant in the class and avoid late to class.

CONTACT

Address: No. 29, Zone 5 Orisunmibare Ogbere Kehinsi Ibadan,

Oyo State, Nigeria. Phone: 08062197769

Email: oyelakintayodamola@gmail.com

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS and Java Coding
- Data cleaning and preparation
- Data analysis and exploration
- Statistical knowledge
- Creating data visualizations
- Creating dashboards and reports
- Writing and communication
- **Problem solving**
- Spreadsheet
- **Data Collection**
- Information Verification
- Googling with Google Searching **Engine**
- **Graphic Design**

• Oyo Data Management Teams' Reviews Meetings 27 July 2022

Organizer: APIN

Oyo Data Management Teams' Reviews Meetings 1st June 2022

Organizer: APIN

- Accelerated Jobberman Soft Skill Training with Certificate 10th October 2021
 - **Organizer:** Jobberman Online
- Oyo Data Management Teams' Reviews Meetings 16 March 2021 **Organizer: APIN**
- Gender-Based Violence Service Assessment and Mapping Agenda for Data Collectors' Training 9th-12th November 2020

Organizer: JHPIEGO

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATIONS

National Youth Service Corps

Directorate Headquarters Plot 416, Tigris Crescent, Off Aguiyi Ironsi Street, Maitama, P.M.B 138 Abuja

Bachelor of Science: Transport Management

Ladoke Akintola University of Technology Ogbomoso, Oyo State.

2019

2012-2018

International Diploma in Logistics and Transport The Chartered Institute of Logistics and Transport International Incorporated by Royal Charter 1926 United Kingdom	2013
Professional Diploma in Logistics and Transport Management. The Polytechnic, Ibadan Oyo State.	2008-2010
Certificate Course in Computer Operations with Merit The Polytechnic, Ibadan Oyo State.	2010
SSCE Certificate. Oke 'Badan High School Oluyoro Oke Offa Ibadan.	1996-2002
Testimonial Certificate. Community Primary School Ogbere Oloba Ibadan	1989-1995

PROFESSIONAL TRAINING AND CERTIFICATIONS

*	HISP_UiO DHIS2_101: DHIS2 Fundamental	11 th August 2021
	DHIS2 Academy Online Course Offered by the University of Oslo	
*	HISP D2EVENTS 100: DHIS2 Events Fundamental	14 th Sept. 2021
	DHIS2 Academy Online Course Offered by the University of Oslo	
*	Introduction To Structured Query Language (SQL)	04 th July 2022
	Simplilearn Online Training	
*	Introduction to Data Analytics	June 24, 2022
	IBM & Cousera Online Class	
*	Declaration of Completion in Tableau Training	20 th June 2022
	Simplilearn Online Training	
*	Declaration of Completion in Power BI for Beginners	11 th June 2022
	Simplilearn Online Training	
*	Certificate of Completion in Data Analytics Using MS Excel	21 st May 2022
	Ifective Online Training	
*	Declaration of Completion in Business Analytics with Excel	12 th May 2022
	Simplilearn Online Training	
*	Certificate of Completion in Microsoft Excel 2019/365	29 st Sept. 2021
	Earn and Excel by Sohail Anwar (Director)	
*	Certificate of Participation in Basic of HTML and CSS for Beginners	1 st March 2023
	OpenWeaver Online Training by Pooja Agrawal Instructor	